spiritualpub.com 2011-11-08

# Spiritual Pub Disclaimer, legal and Copyright Policy

##  Privacy Policy

Our visitor’s privacy is of utmost importance at www.Spiritualpub.com. This Privacy Policy Statement is therefore created to notify you on how we deal with privacy issues in relation to your visit to our site. We request you to read this Statement of Privacy carefully before using SpiritualPub.com and submitting your personal information.

Like most other websites, SpiritualPub.com can collect certain information in regards to your visit to our website such as your browser type,your Internet Service Provider ( ISP ) information, your Internet Protocol ( IP) address or proxy server IP address, the date, time and duration of your visit, the pages you have viewed, the referring sites or search engine, or links that landed you to our site, your operating system information, and possibly other non-identifiable information.

We collect personally identifiable information such as names, email addresses, postal addresses, phone numbers etc., when you submit them voluntarily. This voluntarily submitted information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you permit us to use it in another way, for instance to add you to one of our mailing lists. Be noted that your IP address will be automatically collected, and your names and email addresses are required when you leave comments; however you have the full freedom whether to leave comments/feedbacks or not.

**Use of Cookies**  
We may use cookie and tracking tools in regards to the features offered. For example, we use analytic programs that may use tracking cookies. Cookie and tracking technology help to collect information such as the browsers types and the operating system, the number of users visiting to the site, and help understand how users interact with the site.

We use third party advertising companies such as Google Adsense, Amazon etc., to serve ads when you visit our website. These advertising partners may use cookies, javascripts, sessions or web beacons to gather information about your visit in order to provide related advertisements or to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. If you wish to learn more about this practice and opt out of the use of the Google cookie, visit [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google's Privacy Center").

You may also choose to turn off cookies through your individual browser options in your browser settings. However, this may affect your ability to effectively interact with our site and other websites. Also, to be noted that we have no access to or control over these cookies, sessions, web beacons that are used by our advertiser partners, so please visit their respective privacy policy pages to review on how they use cookies and personal information.

**Distribution of Information**  
We will not disclose any personally identifiable information about you to third party unless you provide us with your consent or we are legally bound to do so.

**Third Party WebSites**  
Our site may contain links to other third party sites and affiliate sites. We highly suggest you to check the privacy practices of the sites that are referenced, listed or displayed here at SpiritualPub.com. We have no control or influence over the privacy policies of the sites to which we provide links; hence if you click through to such a site, please be aware that you will be subject to that site's privacy policies. Make sure to check the Privacy policies and terms of policies of each site you visit for specific information. SpiritualPub.com cannot be held liable for damages of other websites linked, referenced or otherwise.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy Statment**  
We reserve the rights to change this Statement of Privacy at any time, thus, we advise you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed in regards to the changes that have been made. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set out in this Privacy Statement.

**Contact Information**  
We highly appreciate your feedback and comments regarding this Statement of Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or suggestions, please feel free to contact us at **spiritualpub (at) gmail.com** , it would be our greatest pleasure to provide you with any kind of assistance regarding any of your queries or concerns.

We appreciate your visit to our website!
